

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR • FULL STACK DEVELOPER

🛮 🗓 (+91) 875-004-1646 | 🗷 abhishekranjan622@outlook.com | 🏕 www.jarryingnut.me | 🖸 jarryingnut | 🗖 jarryingnut | 💆 jarryingnut

Summary.

I'm a full stack developer aims to create incredible digital experiences through code. My passion for development is unmatched. Every day I wake up pumped to collaborate, design and code. I love every aspect of bringing an idea to fruition and find each step of the way exciting.

Skills_

Front-end React.js, Redux.js, HTML5, CSS, ChakraUI

Back-end GraphQl, Prisma, Apollo, Node.js, Express.js, Firebase

DatabasesMongoDB, PostgresSQLLanguagesJavascript, Typescript, JavaTestingCypress, Jest, React testing libraryDevOpsAWS, Heroku, Git, Github

Soft Skills Problem Solving, Team Work, Interpersonal Communication, Leadership, Intercultural Communication

Education

University Institute Of Engineering And Technology, Kurukshetra University

Kurukshetra, India

Aug. 2017 - June. 2021

B.TECH IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING
Been a bona fide member of Google Developer Student Club, UIET chapter

Personal Projects _____

Gigapost [live] [github]

A SOCIAL BLOG BUILT WITH MERN STACK

- Create, update, delete, comment and like other people's posts
- Redux is used for managing state and styling is done with ChakraUI
- Tests are written in jest and cypress

Thessa [live] [github]

A FULL STACK PERSONAL MANAGEMENT SYSTEM BUILT WITH REACTJS AND FIREBASE

- The application has similar functionality as Todoist
- Authentication and authorization is implemented with firebase authentication
- Cloud Firestore is used for database management
- UI is built with React and styled with ChakraUI and SASS

Lount [github]

A FULL STACK CHAT APPLICATION BUILT WITH REACTJS AND GRAPHQL

- Backend is built with Apollo GraphQl and uses graphql subscriptions for sending and receiving messages in real time
- PostgresSQL and latest Prisma 2 ORM is used for designing database
- · Frontend is built with Reactjs and Typescript and ChakraUI is used for styling

Portfolio Website [live] [github]

This is my personal portfolio built with Gatsby.js

- Used github actions for continuous integration and continuous deployment
- · It is blazing fast.

Experience

Art Of Living Volunteer

Kurukshetra, India

HELPED WITH ORGANISING WORKSHOPS AND REACHED OUT PEOPLE IN NEED

July 2018 - present

Online T-shirt business

Delhi, India

April 2016 - July 2016

DESIGNED AND SOLD QUIRKY GRAPHIC TSHIRTS ON TEESPRING.COM